searchtuner.com 2018-12-30

# 

**Privacy Policy**

**       I.          ****About This Privacy Policy and The Extension**

This Privacy Policy is part of the SearchTuner (the “Company,” “we,” or “us”) End User License Agreement available at http://searchtuner.com/Terms, and applies to all users of the SearchTuner browser extension (the “Extension”) and this website (the “Website”), together with any updates or upgrades that may become available. It describes how the Company collects and uses your information when you use the Extension or this Website.  If you do not agree to all terms in this Privacy Policy, do not install or use the Extension or this Website. You may disable or uninstall the Extension at any time by following the instructions provided in the End User License Agreement.

The Extension and Website may integrate third party content (“Third Party Content”) in order to display what services are streaming certain content and search results to you.  Such Third Party Content may include feeds, search results, APIs, links, information, websites, web pages, services, claims, promotions, offers, statements, data files, images, graphics, software, videos, music, photographs, sounds, or other content displayed, promoted, or otherwise made available through third parties.  Such Third Party Content also may include advertising, or advertising-supported search results, which will be displayed to you if you use the search box or click on services that are streaming certain content. The Extension and Website are exclusively directed for use by adults.  The Company does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us immediately at the email address in the last paragraph below. By using the Extension or Website, you are accepting and agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**     II.          ****Information We Collect**

We do not collect information that can personally identify you unless you contact us and provide us with that information (such as by sending us an email). We do collect information that does not personally identify you (“Non-PII”) through your use of the Extension or the Website. 

**Information You Provide.  **If you email us, enter your information into the contact us page, send us mail, or call us, you may (if you choose to) submit personal information to enable us to effectively respond to your inquiry, such as your full name, email address, telephone number, and other identifying information. Your submission of any such information is voluntary, and you may choose not to disclose any of this information when contacting us.

**Information Collected When You Are Using the Extension.** The information we automatically collect through the Extension while you are using the Extension includes information about your computer and your computing environment, such as your IP address, search terms, URL of websites visited while the extension is active, and your browser type and computer type (also known as “user-agent string”). Likewise, when you use the Extension to click on services that are streaming certain content, submit search terms, or otherwise engage with Third Party Content, the Extension automatically sends certain data to our search partners’ servers in order to return the requested information to you.  This data may include your search query or the term you clicked on, time of day, browser type, default language setting, IP address, unique identifier number, and a code identifying you as a user of the Extension. 

**When Accessing or Using the Website.**   We also automatically collect certain information when you visit the Website, such as your IP address, country code, unique identifier number, hardware, software, configuration, operating system information, browser, language, access times, the content of any cookies that your browser previously accepted from us, usage patterns, number of clicks on our Website, session duration, and referrer URL.  Likewise, when you use the Website to click on services that are streaming certain content, submit search terms, or otherwise engage with Third Party Content, the Website automatically sends certain data to our partners’ servers in order to return the requested information to you.  This data may include your search query or the term you clicked on, time of day, browser type, default language setting, IP address, unique identifier number, and a code identifying you as a user of the Website or Extension. 

**  III.          ****Technologies Used to Collect Your Information**

**The Extension** _._ The Extension may use Javascript, web and DOM storage data, and other tracking and data collection technologies to collect and store data about your use of the Extension..

**The Website.   **The Website may use cookies (including session cookies and persistent cookies), Adobe Flash, pixels, beacons, iFrames, JavaScript, web and DOM storage data, third party APIs, and other tracking and data collection technologies, including an anonymous unique identifier assigned to you.  These technologies collect and store information about your use of the Website, such as web pages viewed, features and content you have accessed, advertisements you have seen, search queries you have run, referral URL information, links you have clicked on, and specific products, services or content you have used or viewed.

**Third Party Tracking and Data Collection** _._  Third Party Content providers may also use cookies, pixels, beacons, and similar tracking and data collection technologies to collect user information when you use the Extension or Website. Third Parties that collect data through the Extension or the Website may use their technologies to correlate your Extension and Website use, and any information collected through the Extension or Website, to other information that they obtained from you or other parties.

**  IV.          ****How Collected Information Is Used and Disclosed**

Non-PII collected by Company may be used by Company’s parent, subsidiary or affiliate companies without restriction. Any information that we collect or receive about you may be used, shared, or supplemented for the following purposes:

·        **To provide and monetize the Extension or Website and Provide Relevant Content and Advertising.**  In order to provide and monetize the Extension and Website, we may use the information we collect from and receive about users in order to deliver content or advertising; to perform market research or measure Extension or Website usage; and to analyze traffic counts, user interests and Extension or Website performance. Company’s search partner will also use the information they collect to deliver content or advertising. We may work with search partners, third party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver content or advertising to you.

·        **To Improve the Extension or Website.** We may use the information we collect from and receive about users in order to improve the Extension or Website, including, but not limited to, improving the search results for the user.

·        **To allow third party service providers to assist us.** We may share non-PII we collect from and receive about users with certain third party service providers who help us manage the Website, or provide Website usage statistics.

·        **To contact you.** If you contact us for support, we may contact you at the information you provide us.  

·        **To protect our rights and the rights of our users.** We may disclose any user information in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of the Company or any of its vendors, partners or affiliates, or any of their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of individuals; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law, subpoena or other legal process or requirement.

·        **To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If the Company sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, the Company may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

**     V.          ****Disclaimers**

**Third Party Content and Data Collection.** The Company does not control any Third Party Content that may be displayed to you when you use the Extension or Website.  We are neither affiliated with nor responsible for the privacy practices of any partners or third parties who advertise or link to any websites, products, services or offers through the Extension or Website, or who otherwise provide Third Party Content.  Once you view or click on a search result, services that are streaming certain content, advertisement or link, you should carefully review the applicable privacy policy of such third party service or site.   Even if a third party is affiliated with us, we do not control its content or websites, each of which may have a separate privacy policy.  We encourage you to read the privacy policies of each site you visit. 

**Security.**  Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the Internet can ever be guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under our control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal information transmitted to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk. If you believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please notify us of the problem, stop using the Website, and uninstall the Extension immediately.

**  VI.          ****Uninstalling The Extension**

You may disable or uninstall the Extension at any time by following the instructions provided in the End User License Agreement.

**VII.           ****Location of Collected Data**

All user information and data may be transferred to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world. If you are a user located outside of the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to, processed, and stored in the United States and other countries where data protection and other privacy laws may not offer the same level of protection as in your jurisdiction, such as the European Union. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above.

**VIII.           ****Modifications to This Privacy Policy**

We may modify the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time by providing notice to you and obtaining your consent to such modification. If you do not agree to any modification, you must uninstall the Extension.

**  IX.          ****How to Contact the Company**

If you have any questions or wish to contact us about this Privacy Policy, please email support@searchtuner.com.  This Privacy Policy was last updated August 23, 2016.
